It's been a while, Tanjiro! Long time no see!
Feel free to make yourself at home!
It's good to see you too!
I'm glad to see you're doing well!
And you too, Tanjiro!
At 3 o'clock, I'm going to brew some black tea
that'll make us pancakes!
With lots and lots of butter, okay?
B-butter? Pancakes?
I barely know what black tea is!
We'll have sweets,
bread, and pancakes!
There you go! Enjoy!
Help yourself and dig in!
How exactly do I eat something like this?
Here, I'll show you!
Ready, Tanjiro? Open wide!
Uh, sure!
Well, what do you think, Tanjiro?
It's so tasty, it's to die for!
It really is delicious, isn't it?
It is!
Oh, and Tanjiro!
When you're done, can you change into this?
永遠の意味
知らぬ君に答えを示す時と
無限に続く螺旋の先へ
、「ホン!
掻き掛け持っている通り、
違いますね?
全ラでも注意さないと、
言うことよ、
なのに食べていくよ、
練習を始めるよ、
友 stepsに変えず、
カリエルってObjectでは
トラネハireでしたが、
エルさんリ何を覧める二人忘れになるよ…
世界それが種だよ、
大家都まórkon huresoすぎている stereo
Get each Damage
Euch got
Oh
I
The Penkannt Town
Don't let you realise
After a Jahrhawd
저희 W.O.S.A
TV
Ready
All right! Try to stay in sync, everybody!
Extend those arms more!
Jump as far as you can!
Good! Now twirl all the way around!
It's important that you stay flexible.
It'll help make all your movements more snappy.
So limber up, everyone, and give me a big stretch!
Oh, no! That's not how I taught you!
I'll show you how it's done. Let's switch!
Here we go!
Hang in there!
This isn't limbering up, it's torture!
All right.
Come on, it's your turn now, Tanjiro!
What?
Are you ready? Here we go!
Flexibility is...
Help!
Hello, Tanjiro Kamado.
I've been waiting for you here for some time.
I can't wait to train...
Shut up, or I'll kill you.
Huh?
Kanroji told me all about you in a letter.
And judging by what she said, it sounds like it was awfully fun training under her.
Huh?
I bet you had all sorts of fun, didn't you?
I've got a letter for you from Lady Kanroji!
Dear Mr. Igaro, how are you?
After training today, I sat down and had black tea with Tanjiro.
Tanjiro's so cute!
Whenever he eats or drinks something sweet, he looks like he died and went to heaven!
Isn't that adorable?
Kamado!
I won't go easy on you like Kanroji did, understand?
It's day one and he already hates me with a burning passion!
This is the training I have in store for you.
I'm going to have you strike targets I've placed while avoiding these whiny obstacles to refine your swordsmanship skills.
Okay, but why does this feel more like...
An execution ground!
So, the people who are tied up in here, did they commit a crime or something?
I suppose you could say that.
The crime of weakness.
The crime of incompetence.
The crime of wasting my time.
The crime of annoying me.
They're lucky to be alive.
Oh no!
What am I gonna do?
You'll be using this.
I'm only showing you once, so pay attention.
And that's it.
To be so accurate while navigating the space between all the swordsmen at such speed!
Let's see you do it.
Please don't hit me!
Please don't hit us!
Get on with it already!
Right!
What an absolute joke.
You called that sad display training?
I'll take you on myself, then.
Now strike me!
Strike you?
Right!
Please don't hit me!
You hesitated.
My hands are totally tied!
Again!
Cramped space or not, I have to land a strike!
You're slow.
It's no good.
I'm too worried about hitting one of the other swordsmen.
Stand up.
Start over from the beginning.
And so the most terrifying training began.
I may be using a wooden sword, but it could still cause serious injury.
I have to maneuver between these poor swordsmen while dodging Mr. Iguro's attacks.
This is dangerous!
Especially since his sword strikes twist and turn in such an abnormal way!
You're slow.
We're both wielding the same kind of sword, so how can his vent like that?
His strikes are able to weave and slither their way past obstacles.
Just like a serpent!
What's worse, I can't unhear them!
The muffled cries for help from my fellow trainees as I swing past them!
Please, please, please, please, please!
They're saying please don't hit me!
I can hear every plea and each one pierces my soul!
Don't hesitate, you piece of trash!
I've never felt tension like this!
My hands couldn't stop shaking!
If I don't swing my sword with pinpoint accuracy, someone could really get hurt!
Sorry!
Ah!
Hey, Kamado!
How are you able to keep going after training so hard with the Hashira?
Because if I miss once, I could injure one of you!
Come on, you guys.
Let's join it.
Yeah, why not?
Oh no, this will make our cut sting, won't it?
How bad could it be?
All right.
Here goes.
You sure?
We'll go together.
Ready, set,
AHHHHH!
That really stings!
Still slow.
If you're gonna strike at that speed, this drill is pointless.
Yes, sir.
Now you're lunging even slower.
Get a grip.
It stings.
You're slow.
You're too slow.
Ouch.
It stings.
What's wrong?
Have you given up, Slowpoke?
I've got to focus solely on battling Mr. Iguro.
In a real fight, if your sword gets caught on something, it's fatal.
Avoid all the obstacles and swing your sword.
It's as simple as that.
My strikes are becoming more accurate.
I'm getting the hang of it.
I can evade Mr. Iguro's attacks.
And because of my training, land my own.
Once you land a strike, and slash one of Mr. Iguro's Hauri sleeves, they say that you're
finished with his training.
Thank you for your hard work!
Leave my sight before I change my mind and kill you, and stop getting chummy with konroji,
brat.
It makes me sad to know that he hated me from start to finish!
It'll just drop it and then stop nothing in your head and turn a внешness.
Once you land a strike, and slash one of Mr. Iguro's Hauri sleeves, they say that you're
finished with his training.
Thank you for your hard work!
Leave my sight… before I change my mind and kill you.
And stop getting chummy with Kanroji, brat.
It makes me sad to know that he hated me from start to finish!
What'd I do?
Let's see...
Mr. Shinazugawa's dojo is this way.
Birdbrain! You're supposed to turn right here!
How dumb can you be?
Oh, we turned right there, huh?
Whoa! Zenitsu!
I'm begging you, please help me escape!
Dojo, dojo, you gotta help me!
Help you escape from what?
I'm not even able to stay upright anymore!
It took me forever just to get this far away!
I had to crawl along the walls,
masking my presence like a lizard!
My life is on the line! Please help me!
Make up your mind.
Either come back to training,
or be killed where you stand!
Please spare my pathetic life!
Please calm down!
Shut up!
Tch, carry him.
Uh, yes sir!
Sorry, Zenitsu.
We'll get through this together.
Long time no see.
I'll be training under you starting today!
I can hardly wait!
Don't get too cocky, kid.
I haven't deemed you worthy of my respect, you got that?
That doesn't bother me at all!
See, I actually don't respect you either!
You stabbed Nezuko!
You've got some nerve!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Mr. Shinazugawa's drills were so harsh.
I could understand why Zenitsu ended up like that.
It was a simple striking drill in which we all took turns assaulting Mr. Shinazugawa.
We had no choice but to keep going.
Until we spewed vomit or passed out.
To make matters worse, there were no breaks.
Even Mr. Igaro let us rest a little bit.
Hmph.
When Zenitsu came too, he berated me as if he were avenging his parents' death.
I hate you, you jack!
Ow, ow, I'm sorry!
Mr. Shinazugawa was especially harsh on me.
If I had let my guard down for even a second, I would have ended up right back in treatment.
Ah!
I can't start my training here like this.
Battered, bruised, and covered in my own vomit.
It's soul-crushing.
Bigbro! Wait up!
Kenya's here?
There's something I want to tell you.
Learn some boundaries.
And I don't recall having a younger brother.
If you don't give me some space, I'll eviscerate you.
That's not like the sibling fights we had.
Do you surrender?
Cut it out, big brother!
Stop talking to me like we're close or something, you freak.
Judging by the looks of you, you're useless.
And if you don't have any skills to show, then quit the Demon Slayer core.
You can't even use breathing techniques right, and you're not a real swordsman.
I can't, but...
Hey, hold on before you go.
I've been wanting to apologize to you all this time.
That's it, Genya. Don't give up!
I really couldn't care less.
Now get lost.
But brother, I...
I've even eaten demons.
Just to be able to fight.
You what?
What did you just say?
You bastard.
Demons!
You've eaten demons!
He's gone!
Genya!
What did you just say?
You bastard.
Demons!
You've eaten demons!
He's gone!
Genya!
How many more days is this torture gonna last, huh?
He's back! He's back! He's back!
Quick, lie down and pretend you passed out!
It's the only way we'll be spared!
Is that Tanjiro?
What the?
You'll be killed, Tanjiro!
What are you doing destroying the building like that?
Please, calm down!
Huh?
Hold on.
What's that twisted, ominous sound that's coming from inside?
Ah!
The old guy's on a rampage!
We're getting clobbered during and after training!
What do you think you're doing?
You could've killed him!
If I wanted him dead, he would be.
We're not allowed to kill trainees,
but I have something else planned.
I'm going to break him beyond recovery!
I tell you what,
if he quits the Demon Slayer core right here and now,
I'll let him go.
How dare you!
There's no way you have that kind of authority!
You can't force him to quit!
And you just said yourself that you had no brother!
So you have no say in what choices Genya makes!
Whether he has skills or not,
he's decided to risk his life fighting demons!
If you're not his brother,
then I'm not letting you stand in his way!
Without Genya,
that upper rank would've beaten us!
So I won't let you hurt him!
Genya's my friend!
Is that right?
Then I'll just go ahead and break you beyond recovery first!
Here he comes!
Focus!
Tanjiro!
Damn brat!
He stopped my fist!
Whoa!
He landed a blow!
Zenitsu!
Get Genya out of here quickly!
Are you stupid or something?
Don't call me by my name in front of him!
There's gotta be a better way to signal to me!
Fudge your house!
He only grazed me, but that kick ripped my ear!
You've really got some nerve taking me on like this!
If you've got a death wish,
I'd love to help you out with that!
Stop it, brother!
You got nothing to do with this!
Let's go!
Who are you?
Let go of me!
The enemy won't be able to focus on us all at once if we split up!
So that guy's your big brother?
He's a total lunatic!
I feel bad you had to-
Don't you dare insult my older brother!
I'm on your side, you idiot!
Just die already!
From that point on, it was a frenzy of chaos and turmoil.
The brawl nearly lasted until dusk.
What were you thinking back there, you idiot?!
I received a formal reprimand from the higher-ups.
My training under the Wind Hashira was suspended,
and I was banned from going near him again.
In the end,
I wasn't able to bring the Shinazugawa brothers together, as I'd hoped.
Not only did I get us kicked out of his training sessions,
but my mark still isn't any clearer,
and I feel like I haven't grown at all from my training.
You definitely have.
After all, you took on the old Wind guy, right?
That's incredible.
You really think so?
Just how deep in the mountains is a Stonehenger's house?!
Is he a hermit?!
I think it's just a bit farther.
What?
Is something wrong?
I hear something up ahead.
This way!
It's… a waterfall!
Hey, look!
This way of Zoge'don's cry…
Thus have I heard,
in the presence of the Buddha!
Weeding Shubhast the action of thought,
tfhatsgrabble v'hara!
Thus have I heard!
If you are able to extinguish your heart and mind…
heart and mind. Even fire becomes tolerable. Welcome, boys, to my training ground.
Thank you.
He says that his left and right eyes have been different colors since birth.
If that's everything, then get out of here and stay away from Kanroji.
But we're friends.
So you are planning on seeing her.
Whoa!
Episode 6, the strongest of the Demon Slayer Corps!